Abdan Hafidz

Surabaya, Indonesia

www.abdanhafidz.com | +62 895601077613|abdan.hafidz@gmail.com| Instagram : @abdan_hafidz Linkedin:www.linkedin.com/in/abdan-hafidz| github : https://github.com/abdanhafidz

ABOUT ME

I was born in Binjai, 11 August 2005. I am currently a Bachelor's student in Artificial Intelligence Engineering at the Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology (ITS) Surabaya. Over the past four years, I have taken my programming skills to an advanced level. In the last three years I have also worked at several institutions in the website development department, technology division, and full-stack development. I have often won National Informatics Competitions for the last two years. I also create content on social media. I have the advantage of being someone who is able to think constructively, logically, thoroughly and carefully, and efficiently in doing my work. The weakness I have is that I am not good at responding emotionally to people's communication because of my nature of always prioritizing logical things over emotional ones.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology	Surabaya, East Java
Bachelor of Science in Artificial Intelligence Engineering	July 2023 – Present
State High School 58 Jakarta	East Jakarta, DKI Jakarta
Mathematics and Natural Sciences Department	July 2020 – March 2023

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Class Representative Council of SMAN 58 Jakarta	October 2022 – March 2023
Division 4 – Head of the Leading Work Program	
MPK Student Council website at SMAN 58 Jakarta	
Digital Literacy at SMAN 58 Jakarta	August 2021 – March 2023
Chair and Instructor	· ·

PERFORMANCE

PERFORMANCE	
3rd Place (Individual) in the Indonesian Computer Science	October 24, 2021
Competition (ISC)	, ,
Nationally at SMA/MA/SMK level	
Organized by Osains.ID Bimbel Akademi	
3rd Place (Individual) in Computers at the Independent Science	17 – 20 October 2021
Olympiad (OSM)	
Nationally, SMA/MA/SMK equivalent level. Organized by Osains.ID	
Bimbel Akademi and PEMA University of North Sumatra (USU)	
1st Place (Individual) DKI Jakarta Province in Computers at the	October 31, 2021
National Student Science Olympiad (OSSN)	
Nationally, the SMA/MA/SMK level is organized by Garuda Sains	
Indonesia (GSI)	
1st Place (Individual) Braindicator Science Competition	July 18, 2021
National Scale	
Organized by CV Braindicator Indonesia.	
Gold Medal (Individual) Mathematics Olympiad Open Contest	
(KTOM)	
Nationally January 2020: 2020 District Science Competition	
Simulation	~
Gold Medal (Individual) Computer subject National Science	September 12, 2021
Olympiad Global Youth Action	
National SMA/SMK/MA equivalent level	1 2021
School representatives (Individuals) at the National Science	June 2021
Olympiad (OSN) in the field of SMA/MA Informatics	
Regency/City level selection in 2021	M 2021
School representatives (Individuals) at the National Science	May 2021
Olympiad (OSN) in the field of SMA/MA Informatics	
Regency/City level selection in 2022	

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer

ITS MabaCup 2023

- Building a Rest API
- Manage Rest API end-point interactions
- Manage databases

Chief Executive Officer & Founder

August 2022 - Present

August 2023 - Present

Feez Edutech

- Lead and perform team managerial duties
- Develop an interactive and creative coding learning curriculum
- Create an interactive coding learning platform online
- Develop a concept for the best online coding learning service

Website Developer – Part Time

April 2021 - Present

EvalatorKSN

- Created an online computer-based exam application website which has been used by more than 7000 users
- Created an event registration website which has been used by more than 2700 users
- Create websites and institutional administration systems
- Server and cloud management

Chief Technology Officer & Founder

June 2019 - Present

Indonesian Student Science Training Foundation

- Created an online computer-based exam application website with proctoring features that has been used by more than 11,000 users
- Created an event registration website that has been used by more than 3000 users
- Creating institutional websites, administration systems and event implementation management
- Create an information system to manage the question bank
- Create an information system for managing certificates and electronic signatures
- Created more than 10 event landing pages
- Create a financial management information system
- Server and cloud management

Website Developer – Part Time

January 2019 - Present

PT Antares Dwima Pratama

- Create a company website
- Create an information system for managing letters and electronic signatures

SKILLS

Programming | UI/UX Design | Graphic Design | AI / Bot Prompting | Competitive Programming | Programming Languages: PHP, C++, Javascript, MYSQL, Python, Basic Go-lang, and Pascal | Framework : Node JS, React JS, CodeIgniter, Laravel, Jquery, Next JS, Express JS | Critical Thinking | Problem Solving | Business | Public Speaking & Communication | Creating Social Media Content | CMS | Copywriting | Basics of Social Engineering | Finance & Accounting